{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Chapter8_2.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "Fate la spesa al centro commerciale.",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1457374682.8485696,
            "question": "Y'all do the shopping at the mall.",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "answer": "fa",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457374307.025306,
            "question": "lui/lei (fare)",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Facciamo sempre bella figura con i nostri clienti.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1457374744.0492384,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We always make a good impression on our customers.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "A volte fanno amicizia con i turisti stranieri.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1457374726.8176963,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Sometimes they make friends with the foreign tourists.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "In the morning they often have breakfast at a cafe.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457374642.2810726,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Spesso la mattina fanno colazione al bar.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Loro vivono in campagna.",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1457374702.745069,
            "question": "They live in the countryside.",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "answer": "Leggete il Corriere della Sera tutti i giorni.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1457374823.0088837,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Y'all read the Corriere della Sera every day.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "Noi viviamo in citta.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1457374690.4500008,
            "question": "We live in town.",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Spesso la mattina fanno colazione al bar.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1456771508.897321,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the morning they often have breakfast at a cafe.\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "Spesso la sera fanno un giro a piedi in centro.",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1456772406.94816,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the evening they often take a walk downtown.\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "answer": "tutti i giorni",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457374865.9612691,
            "question": "Given the definition \"every day\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendono",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1456772375.0922103,
            "question": "loro (prendere)",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "often",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1456772303.8247325,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"spesso\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Di solito il pomeriggio Lucio fa la spesa e Nicolina fa ginnastica.",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1456772274.2666018,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"In the afternoon Lucio usually does the shopping and Nicolina exercises.\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "answer": "Voi vivete in periferia.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1457374861.1682718,
            "question": "Y'all live in the suburbs.",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "answer": "fare bella figura",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456771977.5283408,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to make a good impression\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "pagano",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456515100.4967227,
            "question": "loro (pagare)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "faccio",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456772238.0337439,
            "question": "io (fare)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "siete",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456516361.0998456,
            "question": "voi (essere)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lucio e Nicolina vivono e lavorano a Roma.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456515952.6208096,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Lucio and Nicolina live and work in Rome.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "siamo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456770663.4078257,
            "question": "noi (essere)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "vivono",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456516358.2763014,
            "question": "loro (vivere)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendete",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456770660.728582,
            "question": "voi (prendere)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "fare amicizia",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1456772004.528903,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to make friends\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "sometimes",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456516043.8831694,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a volte\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "In the afternoon Lucio usually does the shopping and Nicolina exercises.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456771862.9494872,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Di solito il pomeriggio Lucio fa la spesa e Nicolina fa ginnastica.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "fare ginnastica",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456771710.1076815,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to exercise\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "ho",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456516041.170102,
            "question": "io (avere)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lavoriamo in una boutique in via Montenapoleone.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456515509.0394807,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"We work in a boutique on Montenapoleone Street.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Tu e Valeria vivete a New York.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456771872.9276528,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"You and Valeria live in New York City.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "fare colazione",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456770951.5651116,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to have breakfast\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "usually",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456771880.1229796,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"di solito\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "a volte",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456771875.7251222,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sometimes\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "every day",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456516205.3398392,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"tutti i giorni\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "chiamate",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456515856.8255281,
            "question": "voi (chiamare)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "fare un giro a piedi",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456771983.5046287,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to go for a walk\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sometimes they make friends with the foreign tourists.",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1456771998.4091446,
            "question": "Given the definition \"A volte fanno amicizia con i turisti stranieri.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "answer": "partono",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456516072.4463043,
            "question": "loro (partire)",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "In the evening they often take a walk downtown.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456516226.047034,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Spesso la sera fanno un giro a piedi in centro.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "Io e Mario viviamo a Milano.",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456515052.7316873,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"Mario and I live in Milan.\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "fa bello",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1456770955.2183485,
            "question": "Given the definition \"It's nice (weather)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavorate",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516201.7960725,
            "question": "voi (lavorare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Oggi fa caldo.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515598.5586019,
            "question": "Today, it's hot.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lucio and Nicolina live and work in Rome.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456770922.7762902,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lucio e Nicolina vivono e lavorano a Roma.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "avete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516089.9560244,
            "question": "voi (avere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "chiamano",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456770931.243255,
            "question": "loro (chiamare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "You and Valeria live in New York City.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515174.781781,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Tu e Valeria vivete a New York.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "fa brutto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516131.0303047,
            "question": "Given the definition \"It's bad (weather)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Y'all read the Corriere della Sera every day.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771021.951408,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Leggete il Corriere della Sera tutti i giorni.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to pay attention",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456770907.7737017,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fare attenzione\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "hanno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771830.4187794,
            "question": "loro (avere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Fanno ginnastica all'aperto.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515155.4202533,
            "question": "They exercise outdoors.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Facciamo un giro a piedi.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516111.9286065,
            "question": "We take a walk.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Mario and I live in Milan.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515285.5659282,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Io e Mario viviamo a Milano.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavorano",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771969.2071962,
            "question": "loro (lavorare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "ha",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516033.5534394,
            "question": "lui/lei (avere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "di solito",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771834.2690527,
            "question": "Given the definition \"usually\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "fanno",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515846.2015028,
            "question": "loro (fare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "fa caldo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771673.5459712,
            "question": "Given the definition \"It's hot (weather)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to exercise",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515851.1012378,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fare ginnastica\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Oggi fa brutto.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771912.509797,
            "question": "Today, it's bad.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "always",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771761.4556618,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sempre\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's hot (weather)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771952.2155993,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fa caldo\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "We work in a boutique on Montenapoleone Street.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456770440.306302,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Lavoriamo in una boutique in via Montenapoleone.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "fate",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771156.3808951,
            "question": "voi (fare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "paghiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771677.5735817,
            "question": "noi (pagare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "prendiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771151.6742735,
            "question": "noi (prendere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "viviamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456770558.5354624,
            "question": "noi (vivere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456770367.0294707,
            "question": "io (essere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sei",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456770938.9564285,
            "question": "tu (essere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "lavoriamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515987.5781035,
            "question": "noi (lavorare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to go for a walk",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516353.4617126,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fare un giro a piedi\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to make a good impression",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456770903.6179998,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fare bella figura\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "pagate",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771971.9431722,
            "question": "voi (pagare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's cold (weather)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771669.3634112,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fa freddo\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sono",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771682.1526828,
            "question": "loro (essere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "vivete",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516191.255398,
            "question": "voi (vivere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "Oggi fa bello.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771237.6139305,
            "question": "Today, it's nice.",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "fa freddo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515160.0519466,
            "question": "Given the definition \"It's cold (weather)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "fai",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515023.5490856,
            "question": "tu (fare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's nice (weather)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515475.7646763,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fa bello\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "It's bad (weather)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456514820.919975,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fa brutto\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "facciamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771714.8625865,
            "question": "noi (fare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "e'",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515177.621635,
            "question": "lui/lei (essere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to make friends",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771898.1580136,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fare amicizia\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "hai",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516310.7059088,
            "question": "tu (avere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "sempre",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515034.488442,
            "question": "Given the definition \"always\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "spesso",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515974.1543603,
            "question": "Given the definition \"often\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "chiamiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456771963.9857957,
            "question": "noi (chiamare)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "We always make a good impression on our customers.",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516188.3519602,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Facciamo sempre bella figura con i nostri clienti.\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "fare attenzione",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516012.122984,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to pay attention\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "abbiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456770913.5847158,
            "question": "noi (avere)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "to have breakfast",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515607.7644844,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fare colazione\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "partite",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456516340.7639966,
            "question": "voi (partire)",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "answer": "partiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1456515842.309297,
            "question": "noi (partire)",
            "tried": 1
        }
    ]
}